In this video, we're going to execute code with a function g that contains a switch
在本视频中，我们将使用函数 g 执行代码，该函数包含 switch c
case statement.
ase 语句。
As always, we begin with the execution arrow at the start of main for
与往常一样，我们从 main 开头的执行箭头开始，
the statement a = g(10, 4);.
表示语句 a = g (10, 4);。
We make a box per a since we're declaring it, then we create a frame for
既然我们声明了 a，我们就为它做一个方框，然后我们为
the function g, and populate it with the values 10 for n and 4 for x.
函数 g 创建一个框架，然后在里面填充值 10 代表 n，用 4 表示 x。
We make a note of where we are and we'll return to when the function is complete,
我们记下自己的位置，然后返回到函数完成的时间，
and enter function g.
然后输入函数 g。
We have the switch statement x + n in this case is 4 + 10 which is 14.
在本例中，我们有 switch 语句 x + n 是 4 + 10，也就是 14。
So we find the matching case label, case 14 and
因此，我们找到了匹配的 case 标签 case 14，然后将
transition our execution arrow inside that case and begin executing statements there.
执行箭头转移到该案例中，然后开始在那里执行语句。
The first statement we encounter is the return statement n- x, 10- 4 = 6.
我们遇到的第一条语句是返回语句 n-x，10-4 = 6。
As always when we encounter a return statement,
与往常一样，当我们遇到 return 语句时，
we're going to make a note of the value to return and leave the function that we're
我们将记下要返回的值，然后离开我们
in going back to the calling function and destroying the frame.
要返回的函数返回到调用函数并销毁框架。
We finished the assignment statement with a = 6.
我们以 a = 6 结束了赋值语句。
Now we reach int b = g(a, 2).
现在我们到达 int b = g (a, 2)。
So we create a box for b, draw a frame for g, passing in the arguments a,
因此，我们为 b 创建一个方框，为 g 画一个框架，传入参数 a，
which is 6 and 2.
即 6 和 2。
We note our position and enter function g.
我们记下我们的位置并输入函数 g。
Here, our selection expression is 2 + 6, which is 8, so
在这里，我们的选择表达式是 2 + 6，也就是 8，所以
we're going to go into the case for 8 and begin executing statements there.
我们将深入研究 8 的案例并开始在那里执行语句。
The first statement we encounter is x = x + 1, so
我们遇到的第一条语句是 x = x + 1，因此
we update the box for x to have 3 instead of 2.
我们将 x 的框更新为 3 而不是 2。
Now we fall through to the next case.
现在我们来看下一个案例。
There is no break statement here, and
这里没有中断声明，
we don't worry about the fact that there is another case label.
我们也不用担心还有另一个手机壳标签。
We just keep executing statements until we reach a break.
我们只是继续执行语句，直到休息一下。
The next statement is n = n- 1.
下一个语句是 n = n-1。
So we're going to update the value of n to be 5.
因此，我们要将 n 的值更新为 5。
And now we do reach a break statement.
现在我们确实达成了休息声明。
This break statement is going to take us out of the innermost
这个 break 语句将使我们脱离最内层
enclosing switch statement, the boundaries which are here.
封闭的 switch 语句，即这里的边界。
As we'll see later, break could take us out of other constructs.
正如我们稍后将看到的，break 可能会使我们退出其他结构。
But in this case, it'll take us out of the switch statement that encloses it and
但是在这种情况下，它将使我们退出包含它的 switch 语句，然后
we begin executing code after the switch.
我们在切换之后开始执行代码。
The next statement we encounter says to return x * n, which is 3 * 5, which is 15.
我们遇到的下一个语句是返回 x * n，即 3 * 5，也就是 15。
So we return 15, return to main, and
所以我们返回 15，返回 main，然后
destroy the frame for g and assign 15 to b.
销毁 g 的帧然后将 15 分配给 b。
Now we have int c = g(9, b).
现在我们有 int c = g (9, b)。
So we create a box for c, a frame for g with arguments 9 and
因此，我们为 c 创建一个方框，为 g 创建一个框架，参数为 9，
b which is 15 and note where we are and enter function g.
b 为 15，然后记下我们在哪里，然后输入函数 g。
Evaluating this expression gives us 24.
计算这个表达式会得到 24。
Looking at our case labels, we have 8, 0, and 14.
查看我们的箱子标签，我们有 8、0 和 14。
None of those match 24, so we use the default which matches anything that's not
这些都不匹配 24，因此我们使用默认值，它匹配任何未
named explicitly by another case label.
被其他案例标签明确命名的内容。
We'll jump into the default case and begin executing statements there.
我们将跳入默认情况并开始在那里执行语句。
We do x = n, assigning 9 to x which brings us to a break
我们做 x = n，将 9 分配给 x，这使我们陷入了中断，
which takes us out of the inside of the switch statement.
这使我们脱离了 switch 语句的内部。
We now return x * n which is 81.
我们现在返回 x * n，即 81。
Back to main, we finish our assignment and return zero from main exiting the program.
回到 main，我们完成任务并从 main 退出程序时返回零。